Hello Hello friends today we are going to talk
about the results of the Russia Com board
which has called for most of the board meetings today
and if you
want updates about such regular stocks then subscribe to our channel
friends let me tell you about this company in advance
so subscribe to such people
like
disgusting
very different small 16 inch and it is the
chief
general insurance company
subscribe from home bluetooth watch
friends in motor insurance there is a lot of
competition Yadav and fire incidents will kill
intensity cement provides insurance one week the
company has another
advantage that ICICI Bank's
parents are either their payment a company with
which retired and insurance sector
insurance answer it is also
with different financial instruments
this company strides
friends they see that there is fixed
tax benefit so today the company has declared
for this the final treatment on you
so if you have as many shares of this number then
you will get these shares  You will
get the ticket for this final and the car accident
date will be declared later,
after that friends, there is another news that the company has
designed to take action against these compliance officers and that is
effective from 28th October and last the
result of this company was declared,
hello friends, the result will remain in the end, so
in almost every quarter it is
of 130 crores
and there is
some difference in 308, friends, it is
very effective, please
subscribe,
it has registered a profit of six crores,
friends, if we talk about this stock, then
this stock almost A Thousand
Seventeen Ugraayudh 46 or even 40, it has
almost doubled, the stock price for
this travel company is a very stable company, the
companies are moving ahead, almost every day
stock price has also doubled, friends, this
company is ready to give a good performance,
good revenue increase last
year, did last year and this is a little
plate in the tweet, so this expectation
is fixed at
25  Very good for long term, very good
company, Edward Channel, Indian Tech